gptboycott.com 2010-12-04

# GPTBoycott.com - Privacy Policy

##  Privacy Policy 

**_Introduction_**

We take your right to privacy seriously, and want you to feel comfortable using this web site. This privacy policy deals with personally identifiable information that may be collected by this site.

**_Definitions_**

**"Complaint Submission Form"** refers to the [complaint form](http://www.gptboycott.com/submit.php) used by Visitors in order to submit complaints about Programs to GPTBoycott.

**"Extra Details"** refers to other details submitted by Visitors to GPTBoycott through our Complaint Submission Form and other forms, including but not limited to their name, as well as any comments or complaints made.

**"Personal Details"** refers to the e-mail address and IP address of our Visitors.

**"Program"** refers to any internet based business which promises to reward or pay for various activities. Some programs require reading e-mails, clicking links or completing online surveys, while others require participation in investment programs or shopping via their website. These types of internet based businesses are known as "get paid to" programs and are the primary focus of GPTBoycott.

**"Visitors"** refers to persons who visit our website or communicate with GPTBoycott by e-mail, including those who participate in the site by making submissions to GPTBoycott through our Complaint Submission Form and other forms, as well as members of our [discussion forum](http://www.gptboycott.com/forum/).

**_How Information is Used_**

Any communications submitted to GPTBoycott.com will be treated with confidentiality and anonymity in mind.

Personal Details collected by this site will not be shared, sold, rented or leased to third parties under any circumstances.

Extra Details may in some cases be made public. For example, Visitors who make complaints against a program which is subsequently or already boycotted, shall have their name and complaint made public on the program's boycott page. Extra Details may sometimes be shared with third parties without being made public in order to resolve complaints, or to further the objectives of GPTBoycott.

However, we make no guarantee of total anonymity in all circumstances. We suggest that Visitors take their own precautions if they desire to remain anonymous. It should be noted that in the case of our Complaint Submission Form, the submission of complaints using a pseudonym for the name field is acceptable, though a valid e-mail address must be supplied to enable representatives of GPTBoycott to communicate with the Visitor while attempting to resolve the issues brought forth in said Visitor's complaint. Failure to include a valid e-mail address will result in the complaint being excluded from those being considered to support the addition of a Program to either the Watch List or the Boycott List.

**_Unsubscription From Our Services_**

In the case of our Mailing List, you may unsubscribe by clicking the unsubscription link which may be found within each e-mail we send.

In the case of our Discussion Form, your account may be suspended on request, by logging in to your forum account, clicking "User CP", then clicking "Suspend My Account", and completing the form therein.

If you have previously suspended your forum account, you may [request reinstation of your forum account](http://www.gptboycott.com/reinstate.php). An administrative charge will be levied for this service.

**_Information that is Gathered from Visitors_**

In common with other websites, log files are stored on the web server saving details such as the visitor's IP address, browser type, referring page and time of visit.

Cookies may be used to remember visitor preferences when interacting with the website, for example by remembering forum account details to avoid making Visitors log in each time they visit our site.

**_Changes to this Privacy Policy_**

Changes may be made to this policy from time to time. In this case a post shall be made in our [discussion forum](http://www.gptboycott.com/forum/) with full details of any changes made. 

**_General Conditions_**

This privacy policy shall not form a legally binding or enforceable contract, but GPTBoycott will use its best endeavours to attain the high standards set forth in this policy. Ownership, management and control of GPTBoycott may from time to time change, for example where a new member of staff is appointed to help with the operation of the site.
